<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Blog</title>
    <link>https://foreveraprogrammer.github.io/blog/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2017 12:50:54 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://foreveraprogrammer.github.io/blog/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The 4 Questions I ask myself before starting a project</title>
      <link>https://foreveraprogrammer.github.io/blog/posts/4-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2017 12:50:54 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://foreveraprogrammer.github.io/blog/posts/4-questions/</guid>
      <description>Anytime I work on a project I ask myself the following four questions to figure out what code I’ll write. I also use these four questions to figure out if I should even work on a request.
What’s the benefit? Examples:
 What’s the benefit of this change? How much will it improve performance? Will it decrease performance? Will anyone even noticed the change? Will it make the code easier/harder to maintain?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Code Examples</title>
      <link>https://foreveraprogrammer.github.io/blog/posts/code-examples/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2017 12:41:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://foreveraprogrammer.github.io/blog/posts/code-examples/</guid>
      <description>One thing that bugs me about most code examples on GitHub is that there are little to no comments explaining how the code works in demo applications.
If you’re lucky the code demo is part of a blog post or tutorial that explains how the code works but if you are unlucky you have to manually look up each line of code to figure out how it works.
One thing I like to do is to create sample applications with comments explaining how the code works along with details about the framework and issues to watch out for.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Blog Post. Not</title>
      <link>https://foreveraprogrammer.github.io/blog/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 23:52:41 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://foreveraprogrammer.github.io/blog/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>So this is not my first blog post.
My original blog was better suited for a documentation/wiki website which is now hosted here.
Originally I hosted my blog on Dreamhost which worked pretty well. Dreamhost made it really easy to setup WordPress but I got tired of paying to have the blog hosted there. So I moved the site to WordPress.com but found that while I could host the site for free I would have to pay a fee per month to modify the CSS.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>